(Dr Hofstadter:)It's fascinating.
(Dr Hofstadter:)How can someone
as enlightened as Sheldon
(Dr Hofstadter:)come from someone like you?
(Mrs Cooper:)I know the answer.
(Mrs Cooper:)You're not gonna like it.
(Dr Hofstadter:)Try me.
(Mrs Cooper:)When I was pregnant with Shelly,
I was driving to church,
(Mrs Cooper:)and I was praying
to the Lord
(Mrs Cooper:)to give me a son smarter
than his dumb-ass daddy.
(Mrs Cooper:)And I looked over
and I saw a Jesus bobblehead
(Mrs Cooper:)in the Subaru next to me
nodding yes.
(Mrs Cooper:)What is that supposed to mean?
It means... I can't believe
we're having this conversation.
(Mrs Cooper:)Well, do it some more.
(Mrs Cooper:)Maybe you can knock
some sense into yourself.
Why don't we all stops
hitting ourselves
(Penny:)and talk about something
safe, you know,
(Penny:)like shoes or how cute
little Chinese babies are.
(Sheldon:)It is not my fault
that your mother likes me
better than she likes you!
Oh, don't flatter yourself!